There will be no leftovers.
Thanksgiving is a horror, mystery film directed by Eli Roth.
After a Black Friday riot ends in tragedy, a mysterious Thanksgiving-inspired killer
terrorizes Plymouth, Massachusetts - the birthplace of the holiday.
Picking off residents one by one, what begins as random revenge killings are
soon revealed to be part of a larger, sinister holiday plan.
Sheriff Eric Newlon, played by Patrick Dempsey.
Jessica Wright, played by Nell Verlaque.
Gaby, played by Addison Rae.
Ryan, played by Milo Manheim.
Bobby, played by Jalen Thomas Brooks.
Evan Fletcher, played by Tomaso Sanelli.
Thanksgiving is a 2023 American slasher film directed by Eli Roth from a screenplay by Jeff
Rendell, based on a story by the pair, who produced with Roger Birnbaum.
It is based on a fictitious trailer from Grindhouse (2007).
The film stars Patrick Dempsey, Addison Rae, Milo Manheim, Jalen Thomas Brooks, Nell Verlaque, Rick Hoffman, and Gina Gershon, and follows a small Massachusetts
town that is terrorized by a killer in a John Carver mask around the Thanksgiving holiday one year after a Black Friday riot ended in tragedy.
Thanksgiving was released in the United States by TriStar Pictures
through Sony Pictures Releasing on November 17, 2023.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics and grossed $46.6
million worldwide against a production budget of $15 million.
A sequel is currently in development.
The film explores themes of small town, sadism,
holiday, massachusetts, thanksgiving.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.